pornblade.com 2019-12-01

# www.pornblade.com

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on pornblade.com

The security of your Data is very important to pornblade.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused. 

This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority. 

## DATA COLLECTED

  * Personal Information:  

    * Non-Registered users can watch videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed.
  * Content Uploaded to the site: Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.
  * Cookies: When you visit pornblade.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. pornblade.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site's features may not function properly.
  * Log File Information: When you visit pornblade.com, our servers may record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.
  * Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * Phone Number: If you join the WhatsApp-Group your phone number is stored to send you our newsletter. To leave the WhatsApp-Group send STOP to the sender. 
  * Push Notification: An anonymized token is stored to send push notification to the browser. 

## USES

  * Your Personally identifiable information submitted to pornblade.com is used to provide to the user the website's features and special personalized features.
  * Your chosen username (not your email address) is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including videos, comments, at, the messages you send through the pornblade.com private mail, etc.
  * Any videos that you submit to pornblade.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.
  * We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).
  * We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the pornblade.com user-experience.

## DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

  * if under duty to do so pornblade.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of pornblade.com or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms Of Service. It is pornblade.com's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party.
  * Should you deliberately upload any illegal material pornblade.com shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and this without notice.   
\- We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

## SECURITY

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We use HTTPS for all resources on pornblade.com 

## YOUR RIGHTS

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by requesting us to do so via the Contact us section. You can unsubscribe anytime you want. For unsubscribe the WhatsApp Group: Send STOP back to sender For unsubscribe Push Notifications: You can do so via your browser preferences 

## OPT-IN AND USER COMMUNICATION

Subscriber's expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, some offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with the option to express the subscriber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes", the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information, including its email address and data may be used for that matter or disclosed to third-parties. 

## OPT-OUT AND USER COMMUNICATION

Subscriber's expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, other offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with a pre-selected preference or choice. If the subscriber does not deselect the pre-selected preference of choice (i.e. "OPT-OUT" of the offer) then the site may transfer the subscriber's personal profile information to the third-party service or content provider making the offer. If the subscriber deselects the pre-selected preference then no personal information about the subscriber may be disclosed to any third-party service or content provider. 

## GOOGLE ANALYTICS

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer to help the website analyse how visitors use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. You can prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. Please note that this website initializes Google Analytics with the setting 

anonymizeIp 

This guarantees anonymized data collection by masking the last part of your IP address. Further information concerning the terms and conditions of use and data privacy can be found at [http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html) or at [http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html](https://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

## THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE

The following list contains all advertisers who may be included on this site. Read about their General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) on their websites. 

## CONTACT US

  * Request access to information that pornblade.com has about you
  * Correct any information that pornblade.com has about you
  * Delete information that pornblade.com has about you

If you have any additional questions: [[email protected]](https://www.pornblade.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)***pornohirsch.com
